<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writeup on Splint3rsec Blog</title>
    <link>https://splint3rsec.github.io/tags/writeup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writeup on Splint3rsec Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:26:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://splint3rsec.github.io/tags/writeup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Russian roulette XSS</title>
      <link>https://splint3rsec.github.io/posts/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:26:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://splint3rsec.github.io/posts/two/</guid>
      <description>Story It all happened during an exhaustive week of studying, the night before having a tough exam in Datascience, where I have to remember all kind of complex math formulas. 10 pm, tired of studying and don&amp;rsquo;t feel sleepy yet, I decided to hunt on Synack for 1 hour before going to bed. And this was the best decision I made that night!
The motivation behind choosing Synack over other platforms is that my friend Conda got into the SRT and I remembered that tweet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admin Panel? Pwned!</title>
      <link>https://splint3rsec.github.io/posts/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 20:54:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://splint3rsec.github.io/posts/one/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, welcome to my first writeup about a funny story of how some admins store their passwords nowadays.
Before you start reading, I want to mention that this finding was closed as a duplicate, so kudos to the first researcher who reported it!
Recon phase After picking a target on HackerOne (won’t disclose), I started my subdomain enumeration… For this step I don’t like to complicate things, I just follow what everyone does for gathering subdomains (which I don’t recommend, always try to be different than others to avoid dupes lol).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
